Daniel J Holmes

Software Developer

(+82)10-8533-7158 | senditholmes@gmail.com | United Kingdom

SUMMARY — HTML CSS JS TS NODE REACT SQL

Education professional with over six years of experience turned software developer. After learning Korean, I naturally gravitated towards new programming languages. Choosing a language, creating a solution, and making something real happen using the power of programming is my passion and my dream is to be part of a team who share that passion.

EMPLOYMENT

English Teacher Time Management, Problem solving

OFFICE OF EDUCATION MAR 2022 - PRESENT

- Created a complete English curriculum for Grades 1-6
- Designed and instructed a year long after-school phonics program

Live Music Manager / Legal Enforcement Agent Salesforce, Data Analytics

PPL PRS - NOV 2019 - JAN 2022

- Performed Data Analysis for use in high level management meetings
- Chosen as a subject matter expert responsible for assisting IT with implementation and development of new Salesforce features

EDUCATION

CS50 Scratch, C, Python, HTML, CSS, JS, React JAN 2023 HARVARD UNIVERSITY

- Mastered the fundamentals of computer programming
- Proficient with algorithms, data structures and computer architecture.
- Completed a fully hosted full stack app using React.

Google Data Analytics | IBM Data Analytics SQL, Python, Excel, Tableau

JAN 2023 UDEMY

- Learned advanced data analysis techniques.
- Performed data analytic tasks using SQL, Python, and Microsoft Excel.
- Completed a full analysis project including exploration, analysis, and visualisation.

BA(Hons) Music Business Management

SEP 2012 - JUL 2015 - UNIVERSITY OF EAST LONDON